[
  {
    "correct_answer": "Singleton",
    "incorrect_answers": ["Prototype", "Session", "Request"],
    "question": "What is the default scope of the beans?"
  },
  {
    "correct_answer": "Iran",
    "incorrect_answers": ["Kuwait", "UAE", "Saudi Arabia"],
    "question": "Which country has agreed to accept the payment of export of oil and petroleum in â‚¹ instead of $."
  },
  {
    "correct_answer": "India and Pakistan",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "India and China",
      "India and Myanmar",
      "India and Afghanistan"
    ],
    "question": "The Radcliffe line is a boundary between"
  },
  {
    "correct_answer": "@angular/core",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "@angular/router",
      "@angular/event",
      "angular-express-route"
    ],
    "question": "Router is part of which of the following module?"
  },
  {
    "correct_answer": "JdbcTemplate",
    "incorrect_answers": ["DatabaseTemplate", "JdbcPluggins", "JdbcDrivers"],
    "question": "To deal with the databases, spring framework provides?"
  },
  {
    "correct_answer": "advice",
    "incorrect_answers": ["point-cut", "join-points", "weaving"],
    "question": "In AOP, the job of an aspect is called"
  },
  {
    "correct_answer": "Anywhere in classpath (including jar fle)",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Specific location within filesystem",
      "Anywhere in project path (including jar fle)",
      "In WEB_INF folder"
    ],
    "question": "ClassPathXmlApplicationContext searches .xml fle in"
  },
  {
    "correct_answer": "util:constant",
    "incorrect_answers": ["list", "set", "constructor-args"],
    "question": "Which tag is also allowed by static field?"
  },
  {
    "correct_answer": "Mud Mud Ke Na Dekh",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Yeh Jeewan Hai",
      "Yeh Jo Mohabbat Hai",
      "O Jaanewale"
    ],
    "question": "Which song is inscribed at the back of the autorickshaw in 'Andhadhun'??"
  },
  {
    "correct_answer": "Deno",
    "incorrect_answers": ["V8", "JavaScriptCore", "SpiderMonkey"],
    "question": "Which of the following is not a JavaScript Engine?"
  }
]
